

Zdeněk Pokorný

Zdeněk is an intelligent scientific researcher who enjoys helping old ladies across the road

Zdeněk Pokorný is a 35-year-old scientific researcher who enjoys helping old ladies across the road, theatre and learning new languages. He is intelligent and

caring, but can also be very pessimistic and a bit moody.

He is Czech. He has a degree in chemistry.

Physically, Zdeněk is in good shape. He is very tall with light skin, red blond hair and blue eyes.

He grew up in a working class neighbourhood. He was raised by his mother, his father having left when he was young.

He is currently single. His most recent romance was with a pick pocket called Aisha Hilda Bryant, who was the same age as him. They broke up because Zdeněk got fed up of being taken advantage of.

Zdeněk's best friend is a scientific researcher called Tyler Richardson. They have a very firey friendship. He also hangs around with Tracey Torres and Barry Walsh. They enjoy bowling together.

Basic Information

Nickname:	Tall Zdeněk
Reason for nickname:	Descriptive
Date of birth:	Tuesday, 16th Oct 1984 (Age 35)
Star sign:	Libra
Nationality:	Czech
Ethnicity:	Caucasian
Social class:	Working class
Religion:	Aetheist
Sexuality:	Unknown
Education:	Bachelor's degree
Course:	Chemistry
Political views:	Far left
Relationship status:	Single
Career path:	Science

Physical characteristics

Height:	very tall
Shape:	underweight
Build:	average
Hair colour:	red blond
Hairstyle:	shaved head, completely hairless
Eyes:	blue
Face shape:	oval
Glasses/lenses:	contact lenses
Distinguishing marks:	none
Other words that might be used:	full-length, grandiloquent, leggy, long-legged, slim, stately, statuesque, tall

Personality

Positive characteristics:	intelligent, caring
Negative characteristics:	pessimistic, moody
Words often used:	caring, intelligent, moody, pessimistic
Other words that might be used:	affectionate, agile, alert, apt, bearish, bighearted, bounteous, bountiful, brainy, bright, brilliant, broad, broad-minded, caring, clever, compassionate, dark, demoralized, discouraged, disheartened, dour, educated, emotional, enlightened, fond, free, giving, glowering, glum, ill-natured, incisive, inexact, informed, instructed, intelligent, keen, knowing, knowledgeable, learned, left, lettered, levelheaded, liberal, liberalistic, literate, lovesome, loving, moody, morose, neoliberal, nimble, numerate, openhanded, pessimistic, prehensile, progressive, protective, quick, rational, ready, reasonable, reformist, saturnine, schooled, self-educated, semiliterate, sensible, sharp, smart, socialized, sophisticated, sound, sour, sullen, taught, temperamental, tender, tolerant, trenchant, tutored, warm, welfarist, well-educated, well-read
Moral:	sometimes
Stable:	sometimes
Loyal:	sometimes
Generous:	very
Extrovert:	sometimes
Compassionate:	very
IQ:	119
Hobbies:	helping old ladies across the road, theatre, learning new languages, bowling, watching sport, reading
Diet	eats meat
Favourite foods:	chocolate cake, soup

Employment

Lab assistant Astounding University 2002 - 2007 re	resigned	
--	----------	--

Junior scientific researcher	Research Me	2007 - 2010	resigned
Scientific researcher	Prof Snooby's Research Hospital	2010 - present	

Background

Early years	Zdeněk grew up in an impoverished neighbourhood. He was raised by his mother, his father having left when he was young.
Formative years	Zdeněk got is first job as a lab assistant at age 18 Zdeněk went to univeristy and got a degree.
Most traumatic childhood experience:	His father leaving when he was two.

Relationships Friends

Tyler Sienna Richardson

(Lifespan: 1987 - present)

, ,	
Relation	Friend
Occupation	Sous chef
Age	32
Relationship	They have a very firey friendship

Tracey Isla Torres

(Lifespan: 1986 - present)

Relation	Friend
Occupation	Receptionist

Age	33
Relationship	They get on well most of the time

Barry Norman Walsh

(Lifespan: 1979 - present)

Relation	Friend
Occupation	Electrician
Age	40
Relationship	They get on well most of the time

Parents

Yvonne Pauline Pokorny

(Lifespan: 1956 - present)

Relation	Mother	
Occupation	Electrician	
Age		63
Relationship	Generally harmonious.	

Nicola Eddie Simpson

(Lifespan: 1962 - present)

Relation	Father
Occupation	Senior programmer
Age	57
Relationship	Non-existent.

Siblings

Filip Ronnie Simpson (Lifespan: 1979 - present)	
Relation	Half brother (shared father)
Occupation	Sous chef
Age	39
Relationship	Zdenek and Filip spent a lot of time together before their father walked out on Zdenek's mum but do not see each other as siblings.

Stella Beth Pokorny (Lifespan: 1981 - present)	
Relation	Sister
Occupation	Sous chef
Age	37

Relationship	They get on well most of the time.
--------------	------------------------------------

Stacy	Beulah	Pokorny
-------	--------	---------

(Lifespan: 1983 - present)

Relation	Sister
Occupation	Politician
Age	36
Relationship	They are not particularly close.

Former Partners

Lyla Gertrude Lopez

(Lifespan: 1983 - present)

(separate production of the separate production	
Relation	Ex-girlfriend (1 year : 2004 - 2005)
Occupation	Legal secretary
Reason for breakup	Lyla wanted somebody more 'badass'
Age	36
Relationship	Remained friends

Helena Denise Brooks

(Lifespan: 1965 - present)

Relation	Ex-girlfriend (1 year : 2010 - 2011)
Occupation	Electrician
Reason for breakup	Helena wanted somebody with a bit more 'grr'
Age	54
Relationship	No longer keep in touch

Aisha Hilda Bryant (Lifespan: 1994 - present)

Relation	Ex-girlfriend (2 years : 2014 - 2016)
Occupation	Pick pocket
Reason for breakup	Zdenek got fed up of being taken advantage of
Age	25
Relationship	Occasional frosty contact

Political Views

Abortion:	very pro
Racial equality:	very pro
LGBTQ rights:	very pro
Subsidised healthcare:	very pro

Gun control:	very pro
Nuclear disarmament:	undecided
Death penalty:	against
Tax cuts for the wealthy:	against
Protecting the environment:	very pro

1984	Age 0	Zdeněk Pokorný is born
1986	Age 2	Father, Nicola Eddie Simpson walks out
2002	Age 18	Starts work at Astounding University at lab assistant
2004	Age 20	Gets together with Lyla Gertrude Lopez.
2005	Age 21	Relationship with Lyla Gertrude Lopez ends (Lyla wanted somebody more 'badass').
2007	Age 23	Resigns from job as lab assistant at Astounding University Starts work at Research Me at junior scientific researcher
2010	Age 26	Gets together with Helena Denise Brooks. Resigns from job as junior scientific researcher at Research Me Starts work at Prof Snooby's Research Hospital at scientific researcher
2011	Age 27	Relationship with Helena Denise Brooks ends (Helena wanted somebody with a bit more 'grr').
2014	Age 30	Gets together with Aisha Hilda Bryant.
2016	Age 32	Relationship with Aisha Hilda Bryant ends (Zdeněk got fed up of being taken advantage of).
2019-1 0-08		Present Day